talk you* for about a minute and ask u
questions to see how your english has been and
what you speak like when you're speaking normally
not being conceaded*
so tell me where you're coming from
I'm from Montreal
Where did you grow up?
I grew up in Montreal
And did you do school in english or in french?
I did uh.. all in french, yep
And tell me about your english
Where did you learn english?
uh.. there is my grandfather who is
anglophone and my uncle so when
dinner or I went to.. in a uh..
I was working
as a flight attendant this summer for Air Canada so I was
practicing all summer
and uh...
with family mostly
Do you have brothers and sisters?
I have, I do
I have one sister and one brother
older than me
What would you say is the biggest difference between you and him?
uh... the way we were educated because
I was raised with my mom and dad and they
were raised only with their
moms, mothers so yeah
ok, good. alright, let's go on